<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Visit Hyderabad</string>


    <string name="p1_name">Sindh Museum</string>
    <string name="p1_description">This museum is home to a vast collection of archaeological artifacts,
        including Gandhara sculptures, Indus Valley seals, and Islamic art.</string>

    <string name="p2_name">Tombs of Talpur Mirs</string>
    <string name="p2_description">Also known as "Meeran Ja Qubba". These tombs are the resting place of the
        Talpur rulers of Hyderabad, and are a fine example of Sindhi architecture.</string>

    <string name="p3_name">Mukhi House</string>
    <string name="p3_description">This is a beautifully restored 19th-century mansion, which is now a museum
        of Sindhi culture.</string>

    <string name="p4_name">Kotri Barrage</string>
    <string name="p4_description">This barrage is a major irrigation project on the Indus River, and is a
        popular spot for fishing and boating.</string>

    <string name="p5_name">Badshahi Bungalow</string>
    <string name="p5_description">The Badshahi Bungalow is the Palace of Prince Mir Hassan Ali Khan Talpur,
        the son of the last ruler of Hyderabad Mir Naseer Khan Talpur.</string>

    <string name="p6_name">Rani Bagh</string>
    <string name="p6_description">This is a beautiful garden, which is a popular spot for picnics and relaxation.</string>

    <string name="p7_name">Pakka Qilla</string>
    <string name="p7_description">This fort was built by the Kalhora rulers in the 18th century, and is now a
        popular tourist attraction.</string>

    <string name="p8_name">Sheedi Monument</string>
    <string name="p8_description">General Hosh Muhammad Sheedi Qambrani was an Askari unit, and also supreme commander of
        Talpur army. He fought against the British forces under Sir Charles James Napier at the Battle of Hyderabad, and
        was killed during battle on 24 March 1843.</string>

    <string name="p9_name">Navalrai Clock Tower</string>
    <string name="p9_description">This clock tower was built in the 19th century, and is a popular landmark in Hyderabad.</string>

    <string name="p10_name">Qadam Gah Maula Ali</string>
    <string name="p10_description">This is a shrine dedicated to the Prophet Muhammad\'s cousin, Ali. The Qadam Gah has
        been a bastion of peace even when Hyderabad was reeling from ethnic riots.</string>

    <string name="p11_name">Kotri Bridge</string>
    <string name="p11_description">This bridge is located on the Indus River, and is a major transportation link between
        Hyderabad and Karachi.</string>

    <string name="p12_name">Hyderabad Gymkhana</string>
    <string name="p12_description">This is a social club, which was founded in the 1870s.</string>

    <string name="p13_name">Hasrat Mohani Library</string>
    <string name="p13_description">The library was built in 1905 as Homestead Hall in the honor of Dr. Homestead, a
        well-known surgeon of Hyderabad. It is the oldest library in the city of Hyderabad.</string>

    <string name="p14_name">Niaz Stadium</string>
    <string name="p14_description">The Niaz Stadium is a cricket ground. The ground has a capacity of 15,000, and hosted
        its first test match in 1973. It was established in November 1961 by then Commissioner of Hyderabad, Niaz Ahmed. Pakistan
        has never lost any match, whether a test or one-day, at this ground.</string>

    <string name="p15_name">Ganjo Takkar</string>
    <string name="p15_description">It is a small limestone range in Hyderabad District, that runs nearly due south parallel to the
        Indus for about 14 miles.</string>

    <string name="p16_name">Auto Bhan Road</string>
    <string name="p16_description">Auto Bhan Road is a major road in Hyderabad. It is located in the Latifabad area of the city.
        The road is named after the late Ghulam Mustafa Khan Auto Bhan, who was a politician and philanthropist.
        \nIt is a busy road with a lot of traffic. It is lined with shops, restaurants, and other businesses.
        The road is also home to a number of educational institutions</string>

    <string name="p17_name">Tomb of Mian Ghulam Shah Kalhoro</string>
    <string name="p17_description">The tomb of Mian Ghulam Shah Kalhora, the founder of Hyderabad, is one of the most important
        monuments of the city and represents the typical architecture of Kalhora’s period.</string>

    <string name="p18_name">Shahi Bazaar</string>
    <string name="p18_description">It is one of the longest bazaar in Asia. The market begins from Pakka Qilla and concludes at
        Market Tower.</string>

    <string name="p19_name">Eid Gah Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="p19_description">It is a large open space that is used for Eid prayers and other religious gatherings. It
        is also a popular spot for picnics and relaxation.</string>

    <string name="p20_name">University of Sindh Old Campus</string>
    <string name="p20_description">Also known as Elsa Kazi Campus. It was founded in 1947 and is the oldest university in
        Sindh. The campus is spread over 120 acres and houses a number of academic buildings, residential halls, and
        sports facilities. </string>

    <string name="p21_name">Boulevard Mall</string>
    <string name="p21_description">This is the largest shopping mall in Hyderabad, with a variety of stores, restaurants,
        and entertainment options.</string>

    <string name="p22_name">Dubbo War Memorial</string>
    <string name="p22_description">The Battle of Dubbo was fought on 24 March 1843 between the forces of British East India
        company and the Talpur Emirs of Sindh near Hyderabad. The battle ground of Dubbo, for the first time earmarked by the
        Britishers. They erected a monumental stone bearing the details of the casualties. Besides the monument lies graveyard
        of Talpur martyrs.</string>

    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about a place.</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>


</resources>